Daniel Sawyer

SOFTWARE ENGINEER / DATA SCIENTIST

Profile

Serious computer scientist with a passion for problem solving, teamwork, and a genuine challenge. I have university research lab level teamwork experience that I believe will transfer over well to industry as I can easily work together with a team while independently solving my piece of the puzzle. I have above average communication skills including public speaking and mentorship, have the capacity to both lead and follow, learn quickly, and work tirelessly until I solve the problem at hand. I can guarantee I will be a good fit wherever I am needed due to my ability to adapt to new and unfamiliar technology quickly, since this is where I tend to thrive.

Employment History

TA / RA, University of South Florida, Tampa

AUGUST 2018 - MAY 2022

- Worked on NSF funded M3X project's vision system for automated grasping with robot arms at the USF CARRT lab.
- Helped teach numerous undergraduate and graduate courses in CSE including Python, Computer Vision, DevOps, and Automata.

Research Undergrad, University of South Florida, Tampa

JANUARY 2016 - MAY 2018

Worked on various projects with professors and PhD students including a NAO robot questions and answers greeter for the CSE department office using Google Assistant Python API and Dialogflow.

Education

PhD Computer Science, University of South Florida, Tampa

AUGUST 2018 - PRESENT

Taking a leave of absence in order to explore job opportunities.

Master of Computer Science, University of South Florida, Tampa

AUGUST 2018 - DECEMBER 2020

• Graduated with a 3.8 GPA.

Bachelor of Computer Science, University of South Florida, Tampa

MAY 2015 - MAY 2018

• Graduated cum laude, 3.8 GPA.

Courses

Check CV Link For Courses, Research Projects, and Publications

References

Sudeep Sarkar from University of South Florida

sarkar@usf.edu

Details

Tampa

United States

813-613-3984

daniel@danielsawyer.com

Links

Homepage

GitHub

 CV

LinkedIn

Skills

Python

Anaconda

Deep Learning

PyTorch

TensorFlow

OpenCV

Bash Scripting

CUDA

C++

C#

Java

Swift

Linux Administration

Git

Languages

English

French

Dmitry Goldgof from University of South Florida

goldgof@usf.edu

Larry Hall from University of South Florida

lohall@usf.edu